Uh
제니와 내가 나눴던 사랑은… 우리를 진짜 우리로 살아있게 했어
The love Jennie and I had made us both feel so alive.
나는 우리를 우리답게 만든 그 모든 기억들로 제니를 계속 살아 있게 할 수 있다고 믿고 싶어
I’d like to believe I can keep Jennie alive
with all our memories that made us, us.
자동차 극장에서 영화를 보던 날들
Going to the drive in.
근사한 저녁식사를 하던 날들
Fancy dinners.
볼링 대결을 하던 날들
Our bowling competitions.
Jennie!
나는… 다시는 그녀를 죽게 두지 않을거야
I won't let her die,
again.
하지만… 지금은 널 보내줄게
But.
I will try to let you go.
덤벼 덤벼봐 계속해봐
♪ Fight me fight me fight me ♪
너 때문에 내가 나 같지가 않아
♪ You made me so unlike me ♪
이야기 하고 싶지 않으니까, 그냥 날 따라와
♪ I don’t wanna talk come behind me ♪
네가 내 운명이 아닌 건 알지만, 혹시 모르잖아
♪ Know you ain’t the one but you might be ♪
누가 널 보낸 거야?
♪ Who sent you, Who sent you, Who sent you ♪
계속 맴도는 널 어떻게 해야 하지?
♪ Who sent you ’round again ♪
나는 진짜 솔직히 까칠한 사람인데
♪ I'm so, I’m so shady ♪
네가 날 휘둘러도 별 상관 없는건 왜지
♪ I don’t really mind when you play me ♪
더 엉망이 되고 싶어, 미친 듯이
♪ Wanna switch it up go crazy ♪
네가 나를 완전히 밀어낼 때까지 떠나지 않을 거야
♪ I ain’t gonna leave till you hate me ♪
누가 널 보낸 거야?
♪ Who sent you, Who sent you, Who sent you ♪
계속 맴도는 널 어떻게 해야 하지?
♪ Who sent you ’round ♪
우린 끝났다고 말했지만
♪ We say it’s over ♪
왜 난 아직도 너에게 이렇게도 매달리고 있을까?
♪ But I keep fucking with you ♪
매번 그럴 때마다, 사랑의 숙취로 고통받아
♪ And every time I do I wake up with this love hangover ♪
너는 술잔을 채우듯 나를 흔들어
♪ You got me pouring for two ♪
다시는 이런 일 없을 거라 맹세했는데
♪ I swore I’d never do it again ♪
네가 오기만 하면 결국 무너지고 말아
♪ Until you came over ♪
너랑 또 이렇게 누워있잖아
♪ I started lying with you ♪
그리고는 이렇게 사랑의 숙취로 고통받으면서 일어 나잖아
♪ And every time I do I wake up with this love hangover ah oh ♪
다시는 안 한다고 맹세했는데
♪ I swear I'll never do it again ♪
아, 망했다, 또 해버렸어
♪ Ah shit I did it again ♪
(전화줘, 전화줘, 전화줘)
♪ (call me back call me back call me back) ♪
아, 알잖아 난 또 반복하겠지
♪ Oh but you know I'm gonna do it again ♪
(다시 전화줘, 연락해줘, 다시 돌아와 줘)
♪ (call me back call me back call me back) ♪
알잖아 난 또 반복하겠지
♪ yeah you know I'm gonna do it again ♪
멍한 상태로 잠에서 깼어
♪ I had woke up in a daze ♪
식은땀이 났고, 입술은 바짝 말라 있었지
♪ My sweat was cold my lip was cracked ♪
한 번도, 두 번도, 세 번도 얘한테 다시 돌아갈 수밖에 없었어
♪ I can’t leave this bitch I had to single double triple back ♪
그녀는 날 떠나겠다고 하면서도 날 놓지 않으려 해
♪ She gon leave me but she wants to keep me on ♪
대체 왜 그러는 걸까
♪ What’s up with that ♪
솔직히 지금은 이런 걸 고민할 여유도 없어
♪ I ain’t even really got time for all that shit right now ♪
난 이제 아이의 아빠가 되었고
♪ I’m a baby father ♪
어젯밤 저녁 식사 자리에서 그녀가 한 농담들, 사실 그 정도로 웃기진 않았어
♪ And all them jokes she told at dinner last night ain’t had me dead ♪
나도 가식이었어
♪ I was playing possum ♪
계산서가 나왔을 때 그녀가 자기 집으로 가자고 했고
♪ And when the waiter brought the check ♪
♪ She said let’s head to mine I said okay awesome ♪
난 그냥 "좋아, 알았어"라고 했지
넌 별로 취하게 마시지도 않았고
♪ Yeah even though ya barely even drink ♪
우린 서로 얘기도 하지 않았지만
♪ We hardly even spoke ♪
난알아, 내일 아침 눈을 뜨면 여전히 그녀로 인한 숙취 같은 기분이 남아 있겠지
♪ But I know when I wake up that I’m still gon feel ♪
♪ That hangover bae ♪
우린 끝났다고 말했지만
♪ We say it’s over ♪
왜 난 아직도 너에게 더럽게 매달리고 있을까?
♪ But I keep fucking with you ♪
매번 그럴 때마다, 사랑의 숙취로 고통받아
♪ And every time I do I wake up with this love hangover ♪
술잔에 나를 붓듯이 나를 취하게 만들어
♪ You got me pouring for two ♪
다시는 너에게 갈일이 없을 거라 맹세했는데
♪ I swore I’d never do it again ♪
네가 오기만 하면 결국 무너지고 말아
♪ Until you came over ♪
너랑 또 이렇게 누워있잖아
♪ I started lying with you ♪
그리고는 매번 이 사랑의 숙취로 고통받으면서 일어 나잖아
♪ And every time I do I wake up with this love hangover ah oh ♪
다시는 안 한다고 맹세했는데
♪ I swear I'll never do it again ♪
아아, 망했다, 또 해버렸어
♪ Ah shit I did it again ♪
(전화줘, 전화줘, 전화줘)
♪ (call me back call me back call me back) ♪
그래, 나도 알아, 난 또 널 찾겠지
♪ Oh but you know I'm gonna do it again ♪
(전화줘, 전화줘, 전화줘)
♪ (call me back call me back call me back) ♪
알잖아, 난 또 너를 찾아 갈거야
♪ yeah you know I'm gonna do it again ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
(전화줘 전화줘 전화줘)
♪ (call me back call me back call me back) ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
아 제길, 아 이런
♪ Ah shit ah shit ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
(전화줘 전화줘 전화줘)
♪ (call me back call me back call me back) ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
아 제길, 아 젠장
♪ Ah shit ah shit ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
(두번, 아니 세번)
♪ (single double triple back) ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
(두 번, 아니 세번)
♪ (single double triple back right now right now) ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
아 제길, 아 어쩌지
♪ Ah shit ah shit ♪
돌아와, 돌아가,돌아와, 돌아가, 돌아와
♪ Back, Back, Back, Back, Back ♪
이젠 내가 무슨 말을 하는지도 모르겠어
Don’t know what I’m saying at this point